Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Communist and Socialist Serials TAM.747
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: International Publications, 1850-2013; cuid11440; 52.6 Linear Feet in 89 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, and 47 flat boxes
  - Subseries II.B: Other International Publications, 1850-2013; 52.6 Linear Feet in 89 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, and 47 flat boxes
    - La Revolution Antiesclavagiste de Mai 1848 a la Martinique: Imprimerie Populaire, Fort-de-France, Martinique, 1967; cuid12914 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - In Struggle's Pamphlets: In Struggle!, Montreal, Canada, 1977; cuid12915 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Proletarian Unity: In Struggle!, Montreal, Canada, 1978; cuid12916 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Bugger Bognor!: Independent Labour Network, Nottingham, England, 1998; cuid12917 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Independent Labor Party pamphlets: Independent Labour Party, London, England, 1907-1957 (Box 229, Folder 6)
    - Jubilee Conference of the ILP: Independent Labour Party, London, England, 1943; cuid12918 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - New Leader: Independent Labour Party, London, England, 1937-1938, 1941, 1966; cuid12919 (Box 54, Folder 16, Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Report of the Annual Conference of the Independent Labour Party: Independent Labour Party, London, England, 1905-1933 (Box 250, Folder 8-10, Box 251, Folder 1-6, Box 252, Folder 1-7, Folder 6)
    - Workers' Control in Industry: Independent Labour Party, London, England, 1919; cuid12920 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Survey: A Journal of Soviet and East European Studies: Information Bulletin, Ltd., London, England, 1962-1965, 1967; cuid12921 (Box 63, Folder 11-13, Box 64, Folder 1-6, Box 65, Folder 1-3)
    - Umsebenzi (South African Communist Party): Inkululeko Media and Marketing Co-operative, Johannesburg, South Africa, 2004; cuid12922 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Cahiers Leon Trotsky: Institut Leon Trotsky, Paris, France, 1978; cuid12923 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Cahiers Leon Trotsky: Institut Leon Trotsky, Grenoble, France, 1979-1985 (Box 219, Folder 1-6, Box 220, Folder 1-5)
    - Journal of the Institute for the Study of History and Institutions of the USSR: Institute for the Study of History and Institutions of the USSR, Munich, Germany, 1925; cuid12924 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - PPSH: Socio-Political Studies: Institute of Marxist-Leninist Studies at the Central Committee of the Party of Labour of Albania, Tirana, Albania, 1986; cuid12925 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Discurso del Comandante Fidel Castro: Instituto del Libro, Havana, Cuba, 1967; cuid12926 (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Problem of Reformism: Internal Bulletin, Middlesex, England, 1972; cuid12927 (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Soviet Review: International Arts and Sciences Press, 1960-1962; cuid12928 (Box 11, Folder 5-7, Box 242, Folder 2, Box 243, Folder 7-8, Box 245, Folder 1)
    - Bolshevik: International Bolshevik Tendency, Wellington, New Zealand, 1999; cuid12929 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Internationalism: International Communist Current in the US, London, England, circa 1960s-1995; cuid12930 (Box 65, Folder 6-8, Box 66, Folder 1-6, Box 67, Folder 1)
    - International Communist: International-Communist League, London, England, 1978 (Box 230, Folder 5)
    - Foreign Bulletin: International Communist Party, Rome, Italy, circa 1950s; cuid12931 (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Bulletin of the International Council of Social Democratic Women: International Council of Social Democratic Women, London, England, 1956; cuid12932 (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - International Marxist Group pre-conference discussion Bulletin: International Marxist Group, London, England, 1968-1969, 1976; cuid12933 (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - Sozialistische Warte: International Publishing Co., London, England, 1939; cuid12934 (Box 56, Folder 22)
    - International Communist Current: International Review, London, England, 1968; cuid12935 (Box 63, Folder 1, Box 230, Folder 6)
    - Der Marxist: International Socialist, 1947; cuid12936 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - International Socialist Congress Resolutions: International Socialist Congress, Brussels, Belgium, 1904 (Box 231, Folder 1)
    - Reports: International Socialist Congress, Brussels, Belgium, 1910 (Box 250, Folder 4)
    - Report of Proceedings, List of British and Foreign Delegates, and Balance Sheet: International Socialist Workers and Trade Union Congress/Twentieth Century Press, Ltd., London, England, 1896 (Box 250, Folder 5)
    - Battler: International Socialists, Fitzroy, Victoria, Australia, 1976; cuid12937 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Chingari: International Socialists, London, England, 1973; cuid12938 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - International Socialist Document Series... - Canadian Right: a History and Perspectives: International Socialists, Toronto, Canada, 1981; cuid12939 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Workers' Action: International Socialists, Toronto, Canada, 1970-1971, 1977-1985; cuid12940 (Box 63, Folder 5-6)
    - ISSS: International Society for Socialist Studies, Amsterdam, Holland, 1963; cuid12941 (Box 63, Folder 3, Box 231, Folder 2)
    - Unser Weg: Internationale Verlags-Anstalt, Berlin, Germany, 1921-1922 (Box 247, Folder 3-6)
    - International (Internationale): International Working Men's Association, Paris, France, 1938; cuid12942 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - News Service: International Working Men's Association, Berlin, Germany, 1931-1937; cuid13353 (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - Internationales Bulletin der Kommunistischen Links-Opposition: Internationale Links-Opposition, Paris, France, 1931-1932; cuid12943 (Box 63, Folder 5, Box 231, Folder 6)
    - Unser Wort: Internationalen Kommunisten Deutschlands, Germany, 1934; cuid12944 (Box 67, Folder 3, Box 206, Folder 11)
    - Grundprinzipien der Internationalen Kommunistischen Stromung: Internationalen Kommunistischen Stromung, Paris, 1976; cuid12945 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - MEGA-Studien: Internationalen Marx-Engels-Stiftung/Dietz Verlag Berlin GMBH, Berlin, Germany, 1994; cuid12946 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - International Socialist Bureau Plenary Assembly of the 10th of November 1906 Official Report: International Socialist Bureau, Brussels, Belgium (Box 231, Folder 8)
    - Texts and Proceedings of the International Conference Organised by the Internationalist Communist Party (Battaglia Communista): Internationalist Communist Party (Battaglia Communista), Milan, Italy, 1977 (Box 246, Folder 2)
    - Communist Party of China and the 20th congress of the cpsu: Irish Communist Organization, Cork, Ireland, 1970; cuid12947 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Youth Bulletin: Irish Young Socialists, Dublin, Ireland, 1972; cuid12948 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Protokoll des Internationalen Sozialistischen Arbeiterkongresses: J.H.W. Dietz Nachfolger GMBH, Berlin, Germany, 1923 (Box 240, Folder 6)
    - Spartacus: J. Lefeuvre, Paris, France, 1947, 1958; cuid12949 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Capital: J.M. Dent and Sons, Ltd., London, England, 1946; cuid12950 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Jahrbuch der Deutschen Sozialdemokratie: Jahrbuch der Deutschen Sozialdemokratie, Berlin, Germany, 1926-1936 (Box 238, Folder 2-3)
    - Tout!: Ce Que Nous Voulons, Tout!: Jean-Paul Sartre, Paris, France, 1971 (Box 206)
    - Jeune Taupe!: Por une Intervention Communiste: Jeune Tape, Paris, France, 1979; cuid12951 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Bulletin de discussions internationales: Jeune Taupe, Paris, France, 1979; cuid12952 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Le Combat des Jeunes: Jeunesses Leninistes, Paris, France, 1934 (Box 223, Folder 13)
    - La Gauche: Journal du Rassemblement Democratique Revolutionnaire/Imprimerle Reamur, Belgium, 1948; cuid12953 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Joven Espartaco: Juventudes de la izquierda comunista espanola, Madrid, Spain, 1932; cuid12954 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Liberacion: Boletin de las Juventudes Communistas de Chile Para el Exterior: Juventudes Communistas de Chile para el Exterior, Santiago, Chile, 1976 (Box 228, Folder 15)
    - Schriften aus dem Karl-Marx-Haus: Karl-Marx-Haus, Germany, 1986; cuid12955 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Issues & Studies: A Journal of China Studies and International Affairs: King-yuh Chang/Institute of International Relations, Taipei, Taiwan, 1986-1988, 1990; cuid12956 (Box 69, Folder 8-10, Box 70, Folder 1-6, Box 81)
    - Die Rote Fahne: Kommunistische Partei Deutschlands, Strasbourg, Germany, 1935-1940; cuid12957 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Spartakusbriefe: Kommunistische Partei Deutschlands / Frankes Verlag G.m.b.H., Berlin, Germany, 1921 (Box 244, Folder 2)
    - Odegetes. Bdomadiatiko Organo tou K.S. tes Kommounistikes Neolaias Elladas (KNE): Kommounistike Neolaia Elladas, Greece, 1997-1998 (Box 253, Folder 6)
    - Die Krise der Kapitalistischen Weltwirtschaft: Kommunistischen Internationale, Hamburg, Germany, 1921; cuid12958 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Jugend Internationale: Kommunistischen Jugendinternationale, Berlin, Germany, 1924-1928 (Box 228, Folder 1-2)
    - RPK (Rote Presse Korrespondenz): Kommunistischen Partei Deutschlands (KPD), Koln, Germany, 1975; cuid12959 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Internationalen: Kommunistiska Arbetarforbundet, Stockholm, Sweden, circa 1970s; cuid12960 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Tiesa: Komunistu Partijos Centro Komiteto, 1966; cuid12961 (Box 67, Folder 9, Box Shared Tamiment 050, Folder 17)
    - Konsequent: Konsequent, Berlin, Germany, 1986 (Box 228, Folder 3)
    - Ediciones OR: El Orientador Revolucionario: La Comision de Orientacion Revolucionaria del Comite Central del Partido Comunista de Cuba, Havana, Cuba, 1967 (Box 227, Folder 4)
    - Unidad, Por la Independencia de Puerto Rico: La Editorial "Pueblo", San Juan, Puerto Rico, 1962; cuid13332 (Box 199, Folder 13)
    - L'Internationaliste: La Fraction Belge de la gauche communiste internationale, Brussels, Belgium, 1946-1947; cuid12962 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Tribuna Leninista: La Liga Comunista internacionlista, Buenos Aires, Argentina, 1934; cuid12963 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Nouvelle Gauche: La Nouvelle Gauche, Paris, France, 1956; cuid12964 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Boletin Libertario: La Union Socialista Libertaria Y De Juventud Socialista Libertaria, circa 1970s; cuid12965 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Youth Militant: Labor Party League of Youth, London, England, 1936-1937; cuid12966 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - International Information: Labour and Socialist Information, London, England, 1924-1926; cuid12967 (Box 69, Folder 4-6)
    - Agenda for the Fifty-First Annual Conference of the Labour Party: The Labour Party, London, England, 1952 (Box 204, Folder 1)
    - British Elector: Labour Party, London, England, 1945; cuid12968 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Festival: Labour Party, London, England, 1951; cuid12969 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Forge the Link: Labour Party, London, England, circa 1950s; cuid12970 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Good to be Alive: Labour Party, London, England, 1950; cuid12971 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - International at Lucerne, 1919: The Labour Party, London, England (Box 230, Folder 3)
    - Labour Party Year Book: Labour Party, London, England, 1947; cuid12972 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Labour's Vanguard: Labour Party, London, England, circa 1950s; cuid12973 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - National Conference of Labour Women Reports: The Labour Party, London, England, 1937-1948 (Box 232, Folder 10, Box 234, Folder 5)
    - On Behalf of the People: Labour Party, London, England, 1950; cuid12974 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Report of the Annual Conference of the Labour Party: The Labour Party, London, England, 1953 (Box 233, Folder 15-16, Box 234, Folder 1, Folder 19-20)
    - Thinking Voter: Labour Party, London, England, circa 1950s; cuid12975 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Town and Country Post: Labour Party, London, England, 1950; cuid12976 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Town News: Labour Party, London, England, 1947; cuid12977 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - We Live by the Land: Labour Party, London, England, 1949; cuid12978 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - What Socialism Will Really Mean to You: Labour Party, London, England, circa 1950s; cuid12979 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Womanfare: Labour Party, London, England, circa 1950s; cuid12980 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - You and Tomorrow: Labour Party, London, England, 1949; cuid12981 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Your Britain: Labour Party, London, England, circa 1940s; cuid12982 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Your Future: Labour Party, London, England, 1944; cuid12983 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Resolutions for the 52nd Annual Conference of the Labour Party: The Labour Party Victoria House Printing Company, London, England, 1953 (Box 233, Folder 17)
    - Labour International Year Book: Labour Publishing Company Limited, London, England, 1923 (Box 248, Folder 17)
    - Report of the Third Annual Conference of the Labour Representation Committee: The Labour Representation Committee, London, England, 1903 (Box 253, Folder 5)
    - Le Proletaire d'avant-garde: L'action leniniste, Paris, France, 1935; cuid12984 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Against Social patriotism: Lanka Sama Samaja Publication, Ceylon, UK/Sri Lanka, 1952; cuid12985 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Lenin: an Article and Two Speeches: Lanka Sama Samaja Publication, Ceylon, UK/Sri Lanka, 1951; cuid12986 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Samasamajist: Lanka Samasamaja Party, Colombo, Sri Lanka, 1957-1959; cuid12987 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - 1905 Before & After: Lanka Samasamaja Publication, Ceylon, UK/Sri Lanka, 1953; cuid12988 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Communist Manifesto Today: Lanka Samasamaja Publication, Ceylon, UK/Sri Lanka, 1955; cuid12989 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - In the Middle of the Road: Lanka Samasamaja Publication, Ceylon, UK/Sri Lanka, 1935; cuid12990 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Paradise in This World: Lanka Samasamaja Publication, Ceylon, UK/Sri Lanka, 1957; cuid12991 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Paris Commune: Lanka Samasamaja Publication, Ceylon, UK/Sri Lanka, 1955; cuid12992 (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - Whither Europe?: Lanka Samasamaja Publication, Ceylon, UK/Sri Lanka, 1950; cuid12993 (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - World Unemployment: Lanka Samasamaja Publication, Ceylon, UK/Sri Lanka, 1952; cuid12994 (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - La Voz del trabajo: Las Organizaciones de Puerto Rico Afilidades al C.I.O., San Juan, Puerto Rico, 1951; cuid12995 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Modern Quarterly Miscellany: Lawrence and Wishart, London, England, circa 1960s; cuid12996 (Box 82, Folder 13)
    - Cloak and Dollar War: Lawrence and Wishart Ltd., London, England, 1953; cuid12997 (Box 82, Folder 14)
    - Marxism, Nationality & War: Part Two National Wars 1848-71: Lawrence and Wishart, Ltd., London, England, 1941; cuid12998 (Box 82, Folder 15)
    - Echange de Lettres: Entre le Comite Central du Parti Communiste de Yougoslavie et le Comite Central du Parti Communiste (Bolchevik) de L'URSS: Le Livre Yougoslave, Paris, France, 1950; cuid12999 (Box 82, Folder 16)
    - Le Bolchevik: Ligue Trotskyste de France, Paris, France, 1999-2000; cuid13371 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Declaration du secretariat unite de la IVe internationale sur l'occupation sovietique de la republique socialiste tchecoslovaque: Le Secretariat Unifie de la Ive Internationale, 1968; cuid13000 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - LSA/LSO Internal Information Bulletin: League for Socialist Action/Ligue Socialiste Ouvriere and The Revolutionary Marxist Group, Toronto, Canada, 1976-1977; cuid13001 (Box 31, Folder 3, Box 228, Folder 17)
    - LSA-LSO Discussion Bulletin: League for Socialist Action/Ligue Socialiste Ouvriere and The Revolutionary Marxist Group, Toronto, Canada, 1976-1980; cuid13002 (Box 31, Folder 1-2, Box 228, Folder 13)
    - Marxist: Leeds University Union Marxist Society, Leeds, England, circa 1920s; cuid13003 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Les Cahiers du Centre d'Etudes Socialistes: Les Cahiers du Centre d'Etudes Socialistes, Paris, France, 1968 (Box 229, Folder 1)
    - Recherches Internationales: a la Lumiere du Marxisme: Les Editions de la Nouvelle Critique, Paris, France, 1963; cuid13004 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Cahiers Rouges: Les Presses Rapides- Limoges, Paris, France, 1955; cuid13005 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Bulletin pour L'etranger: L'etranger du comite central du pci, Rome, Italy, 1959-1960; cuid13006 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Heroes and Heroines of the Libertarian Armed Forces of South Vietnam: Liberation Editions, South Vietnam, 1965; cuid13007 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - A Luta de Classe: Liga Communista, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, 1931; cuid13374 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Boletim Da Oposicao: Liga Comunista Do Brazil, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, 1931-1932; cuid13008 (Box 37, Folder 0)
    - Boletim da Oposicao: Liga Comunista Do Brazil, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, 1932; cuid13349 (Box 155, Folder 13)
    - Contra la Corriente: Liga Obrera Revolucionaria, Montevideo, Uruguay, 1946; cuid13009 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Bulletin Interieur: Ligue Communiste, 1931; cuid13010 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Ligue Communiste: Ligue Communiste, Paris, France, 1972 (Box 229, Folder 3)
    - Le Bolchevik: Ligue Trotskyste de France, Paris, France, 1976, 1999; cuid13011 (Box 17, Folder 4, Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Bulletin de Documentation: L'Internationale Communiste, Paris, France, circa 1940s; cuid13012 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Labor Forum: Lloyd Ross Forum, New South Wales, Australia, 1991-1992; cuid13013 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - London Socialist Historians Group Newsletter: London Socialist Historians Group, London, England, 1999-2006; cuid13014 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - London Voice: London Voice, London, England, 1969; cuid13015 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Courant Alternatif: l'Organisation Communiste Libertaire, Reims, France, 1995; cuid13016 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Communisme: l'Organisation Communiste Revolutionnaire en France, France, 1946; cuid13017 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - L'internationale: L'Union Communiste, Paris, France, 1934-1936; cuid13018 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Notre Republique: L'Union Democratique du Travail, Paris, France, 1962-1969; cuid13343 (Box 137, Folder 1-5, Box 138, Folder 1-4, Box 139)
    - L'Avant-Garde: M.-L Bouxain, Brussles, Belgium, 1945-1946; cuid13019 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Communistische Notities: Maandbland, Amsterdam, Holland, 1974-1977; cuid13020 (Box 73, Folder 4-7, Box 224, Folder 8)
    - India: Marx Memorial Library & Workers' School, London, England, circa 1940s; cuid13021 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Red Dawn: Marxist-Leninist Communist Party-Foundation, Koln, Germany, 1995; cuid13022 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - The "Anti-Climax": The Concluding Chapter of my Russian Diary "The Bolshevik Myth": Maurer & Dimmick, Berlin, Germany, 1925; cuid13023 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - An Open Letter to the Workers of India: Merit Publishers, Calcutta, India, 1939; cuid13024 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Leon Trotsky: The man & his action: Merit Publishers, Calcutta, India, circa 1950s; cuid13025 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - To the Toilers of the East: Merit Publishers, Calcutta, India, 1970; cuid13026 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - What is Insurrection: Militant Club, Calcutta, India, 1948; cuid13027 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Militant for Revolutionary Socialism: Militant Group in the Labour Party, London, England, 1937; cuid13028 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Fables for Our Times "Automation": Militant reprint, 1958; cuid13029 (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Cahiers du Monde Russe et Sovietique: Mouton & Co., Paris, France, 1960; cuid13030 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Giustizia e Liberta: Movimento di Unificazione Socialista, Paris, France, 1935-1937 (Box 227, Folder 15)
    - Giustizia e Liberta: Movimento di Unificazione Socialista, Paris, France, 1937; cuid13372 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Fuerza Socialista: Movimiento por el Socialismo, Santo Dominigo, Dominican Republic, 1981; cuid13031 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Boletin de Discusion: MPI, San Juan, Puerto Rico, 1967-1968; cuid13346 (Box 155, Folder 15)
    - Controversy: The Socialist Forum: National Labour Press, Ltd., London, England, 1938; cuid13032 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Comment: National Office of the Co-operative Commonwealth Federation, Ottawa, 1957 (Box 224, Folder 5)
    - Links: New Course Publications, New South Wales, Australia, 1994; cuid13033 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Socialist Leader: New Leader Ltd., London, England, 1951; cuid13034 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Socialist Leader: New Leader/National Labour Press, printer, London, England, 1949, 1969; cuid13035 (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Utopie kreativ: New Newspaper management, Berlin, Germany, 2000-2001; cuid13036 (Box 32, Folder 1-3, Box 171, Folder 9)
    - 20th Congress (CPSU) and World Trotskyism: New Park Publications, LTD, London, England, 1957; cuid13037 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Culture and Socialism and a Manifesto Art and Revolution: New Park Publications, Ltd., London, England, 1962; cuid13038 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - New Socialist: New Socialist, Toronto, Canada, 2001; cuid13039 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Labour News Bulletin: New Zealand Labour Party, Wellington, New Zealand, 1945; cuid13040 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - How the Labour Party Began: Newsletter, London, England, 1961; cuid13041 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Nickel Belt New Democrat: Nickel Belt Provincial Riding Association, London, England, circa 1950s; cuid13042 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Contra Komintern: Niebelungen-Verlag, Berlin, Germany, 1938; cuid13043 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - MOCT-MOST: Economic Journal on Eastern Europe and the Soviet Union: Nomisma, Bologna, Italy, 1990-1991; cuid13044 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Against Soviet Social-Imperialism and for national Liberation: Norman Bethune Institute, Toronto, Canada, 1976; cuid13045 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - People's Canada Daily News: Norman Bethune Institute, Toronto, Canada, 1972-1973; cuid13046 (Box 36, Folder 5-6)
    - Gauche Socialiste: Nouvelles Publications Internationales, Montreal, Canada, 1986; cuid13047 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Nigerian Socialist: O. Oni, Ibadan, Nigeria, 1967; cuid13048 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Topics: Ontario CCF Youth, Ontario, 1953-1954 (Box 221, Folder 5)
    - Det Nye Arbejderblad: Organ for Revolutionaere Kommuniste, 1947, 1953; cuid13049 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - George Valentinovich Plekhanov: Organ of the Bolshevik Samasamaja Party, Ceylon, UK/Sri Lanka, 1949; cuid13050 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - For a Lasting Peace, for a People's Democracy: Organ of the Information Bureau of the communist Parties in Belgrade and Bucharest, Belgrade, Serbia, 1947-1948, 1955; cuid13051 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Le Drapeau Rouge: Organ of the Swiss Communist Party for French-speaking Switzerland, Geneve, switzerland, 1948; cuid13052 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - l'Humanite Rouge: Organe Central Du Parti Communiste Marxiste-Leniniste, Paris, France, 1980; cuid13053 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - La Gauche: Organe de Combat Socialiste: Organe de Combat Socialiste, 1967-1968; cuid13054 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Le Drapeau Rouge: Organe du Parti Communiste Suisse pour la Suisse romande, Paris, France, 1934; cuid13055 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Correspondance socialiste internationale: Organe Mensuel de L'Internationalism Militant, Paris, France, 1960; cuid13056 (Box 2, Folder 19, Box 151, Folder 11)
    - Correspondances Socialistes: Organe mensuel de l'internationalisme militant, Paris, France, 1939; cuid13057 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - La Jeune Garde: Organe Mensuel des Jeunesses Socialistes Ouvrieres et Paysannes, Paris, France, 1939; cuid13058 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - International Correspondence: The Organising Committee for the Reconstruction of the Fourth International, Hampshire, England, 1977; cuid13326 (Box 199, Folder 8)
    - El Militante: Organizacion Revolutionaria de Trabajadores, Spain, 1978-1979; cuid13059 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Comunismo: organo central en castellano del grupo comunista internacionalista, Brussels, Belgium, 1984; 1992; cuid13060 (Box 32, Folder 12)